42
I could tell you but I'd have to permanently ban you
Sure... Why not
C̕҉̫̭̫͉̜̳͈̭ͅò̡̖̫̤̲̀n̞̞̙̝ş̵͉̦̮i͍̦d͏̲̭̞͞e̷̷̖r̟ ̴̖̳̪ì̶͕̹͖͇͔t̩̯̤̥̫͞ ̳͕̗̭͕͇̞d̼̼͚͈̭̖̫o̭̪̗͜n̡̲̖̯̞̼͍̝͔͘͝e̖̮̳͉͉
Don't quit your day job
The internet says no
Ask me if I care
You wish
It'll probably be nerfed in the next patch anyway
Help. I'm trapped in a Magic 8 Ball factory!
Im recieving some sort of tachyon interference
Ask again after the apocalypse
*Catchy elevator music plays*
...
You've got to be kidding
What kind of question is that?
Error 'nullptr' was not declared in this scope
What's the worst that could happen?
Dear God no
Swipe left
Swipe right
Please drink verification can
Yes
No
Maybe
Ask again later
Kappa
You can probaly answer this one yourself
Have you tried punching anything yet?
Do it, but make sure someone is filming you
Achievement Unlocked: Stupid Question, Stupid Answer
Absolutely
I... I don't know tha- AAAAAAAAHHHHHHHGGGGHHH
My hovercraft is full of eels
Do you feel lucky punk?
LUL
Jebaited
VoteYea
VoteNay
NotLikeThis
WutFace
You should probably consult a professional on that one, or at least wikipedia
Do I look like google to you?
I flipped a coin and it landed on heads
I flipped a coin and it landed on tails
I flipped a coin and it landed on it's side
That question actually tilted me
Let's ask the NSA guys monitoring this chat
Only if you were born on a Thursday in the middle of January
Oh, unlucky
What do you want to hear?
Insufficient data for a meaningful answer
It's a secret